# **Aaron Henderson**

#### **Staff Pharmacist**

Cheltenham, PA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Aaron-Henderson/f7527c971b4fc4f4

Pennsylvania-licensed, retail pharmacist with seven years of experience in providing pharmacy services in a community setting. Extensive history of providing patient-oriented service to costumers. Well versed in medical terminology and abbreviations and dealing with other health care professionals. Open to opportunities to engage in patient care interaction and counseling.

#### License

Pennsylvania State Board of Pharmacy, license # [...]

#### Professionals Skills

- Proficient in the various standards and procedures for maintaining HIPAA compliance
- · Authorized to administer injectables
- Certified in CPR
- Adept at working with a myriad of insurance providers
- · Experienced in training junior pharmacists and pharmacy staff

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **Staff Pharmacist**

CVS Pharmacy - Ambler, PA - October 2011 to December 2015

- Immunizing patients against various viral and bacterial pathogens
- Filling more than 2,000 prescriptions weekly
- Educating the public about adverse drug events and harmful drug interactions
- · Compounding of suspensions and ointments for oral and topical use
- · Maintaining an inventory of prescriptions and pharmaceutical supplies
- · Supervising and training of pharmacy technicians
- Providing up to date information to clinicians upon request

# Microbiology Technician not certified

Thomas Jefferson University Hospital - Philadelphia, PA - April 2001 to September 2007

# Pathology Laboratory Research Technician

Thomas Jefferson University Hospital - Philadelphia, PA - November 1999 to April 2001

#### **Biology Laboratory Technician**

Lincoln University, PA - December 1998 to November 1999

Lincoln University, Lincoln University, PA

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Doctor of Pharmacy in Student Internships**

Temple University School of Pharmacy - Philadelphia, PA August 2007 to May 2011

Temple University Hospital - Philadelphia, PA May 2009

# **BS** in Microbiology

Lincoln University, Lincoln University December 1998

# SKILLS

immunization (5 years), compounding (5 years), MTM (5 years)

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

# **Pharmacist**

September 2016

# **Immunization Certification**

September 2014 to September 2016 Providing immunizations via injectables